const quizDATA= [
	
	{
		question: "Let's start out with something easy. Who first played Message in a Bottle?",
		option1: "MEGADETH",
		option2: "OZZY",
		option3: "KORN",
		option4: "THE POLICE",
		answer: 4
	},
	
	{
		question: "Lets do something a little harder now. Which band was famous for spitting fire during a concert?",
		option1: "ALICE COOPER",
		option2: "Dragonforce",
		option3: "KISS",
		option4: "LITA FORD",
		answer: 3
	},
	
	{
		question: "Which instrument did Charlie Watts play?",
		option1: "None, he was a singer",
		option2: "Drums",
		option3: "Bass",
		option4: "Lead guitar",
		answer: 2
	},
	
	{
		question: "Which one is NOT a real genre of music?",
		option1: "folk metal",
		option2: "indie metal",
		option3: "Deathcore",
		option4: "crust punk",
		answer: 2
	},
	
	{
		question: "Who bit the head off a bat in 1982?",
		option1: "Marilyn manson",
		option2: "jimi hendrix",
		option3: "ozzy osbourne",
		option4: "Alice Cooper",
		answer: 3
	},
	
	{
		question: "Which group recorded the song \"Pictures of Lily\" in 1967?",
		option1: "The Who",
		option2: "The Rolling Stones",
		option3: "The Beatles",
		option4: "None of them",
		answer: 1
	},
	
	{
		question: "Which group started out with five members?",
		option1: "The Trogs",
		option2: "All of them",
		option3: "The Kinks",
		option4: "The Beatles",
		answer: 4
	},
	
	{
		question: "In 1970, The Who told us there was no cure for what kind of blues?",
		option1: "cabin fever",
		option2: "summertime",
		option3: "rock n roll",
		option4: "cheatin\' heart",
		answer: 2
	},
	
	{
		question: "Which of the following Beatles hits contains an antonym?",
		option1: "Hello, Goodbye",
		option2: "Yellow Submarine",
		option3: "Penny Lane",
		option4: "Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da",
		answer: 1
	},
	
	{
		question: "In 1964 the Drifters released \"Under the Boardwalk\". Which group did a cover of it in 1965?",
		option1: "The Rolling Stones",
		option2: "None of them",
		option3: "The Beatles",
		option4: "The Who",
		answer: 1
	},
	
	
];